Tell me,
could it be that
my dad is now
with these stars too,
in the distant galaxy,
watching me?
Maybe.
Hey,
are you okay?
Why are you crying all of a sudden?
Alright, stop crying. We're almost home.
I feel terrible.
You.
Please help take off her shoes.
Why don't you take care of your own daughter?
I can't get out of here.
Please help take care of her.
Are you crazy?
Who are you talking to?
Thank you.
Thank you, thank you.
Don't touch me.
It's okay.
This is outrageous.
I want some water.
Please help get a glass of water.
Get it yourself if you want some.
Why are you yelling at her?
She had too much to drink.
Just help get a glass of water.
Thank you.
Fine, this is the last time.
Please feed him.
Are you done?
Please help me.
Drink some water.
I haven't removed my makeup.
Help me remove my makeup.
Could you do me another favor?
Go to sleep.
I haven't removed my makeup yet.
Wait for me here.
Okay, Mr. Ling.
My Yangyang is back.
Father,
I'm back.
Come with me.
This is unreasonable.
Outrageous.
So disgusting.
I can't believe I ended up like this.
Father.
Today's premiere was very successful.
I've put you in the company
and invested so many resources and cash.
If you still can't do it right,
there's no need to come see me again.
Yes.
How did you handle that little influencer?
It's all taken care of.
Such a small matter
caused so much negative public opinion.
You can't even control a minor artist.
You're in the company every day.
What exactly do you do?
Father, I assure you
she will no longer have
any impact on our company.
You must maintain that group well.
It is directly related to
the commercial interests behind our family,
which is the meaning of Shengli Media's existence.
I understand, Father.
I promise I will do it well.
Wait.
From now on,
let me know in advance if you come home.
Ling Yang has grown up.
I don't want him to have much contact with you.
Understood, Father.
Did you have fun today?
Brother.
Brother, why are you here?
Are you staying at home tonight?
Brother.
Let's go.
I will give you what you deserve.
I've been with you for so many years.
Now that you have money, you want to dump me?
Enough.
I won't give you a penny less.
Just leave.
You bastard.
Is it because of that bitch?
Say something, Ling Hengsheng.
Say something!
Take her away.
Ling Hengsheng, you bastards!
Let me go!
From today on, you move out.
I've arranged everything.
Don't be unhappy.
I'll keep you company tonight.
Okay?
What are you doing?
You're always like this when you come back from home.
Since you're not happy,
don't go back anymore.
I see your dad never treats you well.
He
never treated you as his own son.
Don't fight with your brother anymore.
We can live well on our own.
Right?
What did you say?
Let me go!
Let me tell you,
I am his biological son.
If you didn't look somewhat like that woman,
did you really think you were good enough for me?
Someone hit you?
Yes.
My people wouldn't lay a hand on you.
Maybe it was a fan.
Also,
how could you get physical in the room?
Just as things were calming down,
you messed up again.
Don't talk to me about this.
Call that Mu Cheng over here right now.
I've never been bullied in my life.
Mu Cheng has a live stream...
Right now,
you must call her over here.
Hello, Mr. Ling.
I'm at the hospital now.
The girl is quite seriously injured.
Handle it yourself.
Give her however much money she wants.
Just don't let her bother me again.
Mr. Ling.
Ling Ze.
The girl is unwilling to settle right now.
Tell her to come here right now.
She says...
I must have a word with her today.
she wants to sue you in court.
Wait a moment.
Mr. Ling.
I can't wait.
I'm afraid you'll have to handle this personally.
How much money have I spent on this bitch?
Or...
How is she treating me now?
You go talk to this girl.
The girl is quite emotional right now,
so she probably won't agree to a settlement easily.
I got it.
I'm just afraid...
Call Mu Cheng over here right now.
Mr. Ling.
I said wait a moment.
No matter what method you use,
suppress this matter for me.